I thought you were in Cebu?
How did you know?
[JAO] Got any plans tomorrow?
Nope.
[JAO] Good.
[HAN BIN] Are you here to accuse me of more crazy things?
[ARIEL] It’s okay!
I like you for Pearl.
I don’t think she likes me.
It’s your fault.
It’s because you don’t express your true feelings,
you’re always so serious around her.
What should I do?
[JAO] Are these the mangroves?
- [JAO] Amazing. - Ruth, Jao.
Hi, Ruth! Nice to meet you.
Ruth knows everything about me.
I whisper to her all my doubts.
You should try talking to her too.
[JAO] She said I should tell you myself.
What is it?
I want more than friendship, Kara.
I want to get to know you more.
Jao, I’m hard to love.
We won’t rush anything.
I won’t let you drown.
[HAN BIN] Hello!
- Hi! - Hi!
[GUEST] You look like a K-pop star.
Are you single or taken?
[HAN BIN] I’m single
but my heart is already taken.
[KARA] The key to good surfing is timing.
[JAO] You have to learn how to be one with the waves.
[WOMAN] Jao!
Hey!
What’s up?
[JAO] What are you doing here?
I’m on vacation!
Can’t believe I ran into you.
I’ve missed you!
- Unbelievable. - [WOMAN GIGGLES]
Uh, Kara, this is Lexi.
- Lexi, Kara. - Hello!
-Hi! - Kara.
- Lexi. - Jao’s friend.
Nice to meet you!
Jao and I go way back.
He’s like a brother to me.
And this one is like a little sister to me.
She’s always traveling by herself
and always on dating apps.
[LEXI] Excuse me! That’s not true! You…
- That’s false information! - [JAO LAUGHS]
It’s not true!
Anyway, where’s Allie?
I don’t know.
You don’t know, like, she’s in Manila?
Maybe. Or somewhere else.
We broke up, Lex.
What?
No, you’re joking.
[LEXI] You broke up?
[ALON BY JL]
[LEXI] I’m so sorry to hear that.
Are you okay?
Have you cried it out? Have you moved on?
Slow down.
And I’m very good, actually.
It’s just that you and Allie were together for so long.
[LEXI] I mean, I’m sure this is hard for you!
But, you know, we all saw this coming.
[LEXI] I’m sorry to say this, okay?
But Allie’s been very flaky and indecisive.
I mean, like…
she keeps leaving and then showing up again.
I mean, yeah, you guys look good together, but,
honestly…
you two are more like people trying to make it work
than two people who naturally fit.
Actually, you know…
it seems like you and Kara have more chemistry!
[LEXI] Okay! Anyway!
Enough stressing out.
Let’s move on.
I don’t want to talk about Allie anymore.
Good idea.
What about you? How are you?
I’m fine.
Enjoying Siargao, enjoying my trip.
Do you have friends here?
How many days have you been here?
I’m here alone.
And I've only been here for two days.
I was even planning on staying for another month.
There goes the curse.
[LEXI GROANS] The curse is real!
[LEXI ]I don’t want to leave, I don’t want to go home...
- [KARA LAUGHS] - I don’t want to go back to work…
but I have to go back to work. Why do we have to work?
I don’t want to work anymore.
Jeez.
What do you mean, "curse is real"?
I'm sure you met someone here. Right?
Seriously?
You’ll meet a lot of people here.
Just be careful…
You don’t want to get your heart broken, right?
You know,
it's the people Lex meets who should be worried.
You’ve made a lot of men cry, right?
You’re impossible! That’s not true!
Those were tears of joy!
- Very joyful tears! - [KARA LAUGHS]
- Very joyful tears! - [JAO] Oh, please.
Have you gone on a tour yet?
No.
What are you doing on Thursday?
Jao and I can show you around.
I’m up for it!
Where are we going?
We’ll plan it out.
- [LEXI] Yay! - [KARA LAUGHS]
- [JAO] So going back to your dating life... - Where would you recommend...
[JAO] No, no, no. Don’t change the topic, Lex.
- Who did you meet? I know you. - [LEXI] Where’s the best place...
…you’re not leaving because...
- [JAO] Lex would only stay if... - [LEXI LAUGHS]
[QUINITO EXHALES CONTENTEDLY]
[HAN BIN] Are you okay, bro?
I got friendzoned, bro.
[QUINITO] It’s okay, though.
I respect Pearl’s feelings.
It’s okay, bro.
At least now, you’re free to do other things.
And there are lots of pretty girls out there!
Enjoy the island!
You’re right! You’re right, brother.
Enjoy the island, that’s what I’m here for.
Not to get my heart broken!
Yeah!
And if you want, I can give you a free tour, free drink.
Whatever you want, just let me know.
Thank you, brother.
I’m so happy to have a brother like you in Siargao.
Bro,
we are your family here,
so don’t be sad.
Be always happy.
- [QUINITO CHUCKLES] - [HAN BIN] Okay?
Jao! Join us!
Looks like you’re having a serious conversation there.
[QUINITO] At least Jao...
always seems happy with Kara.
[JAO] Nah.
I’m just a happy guy.
When you first came here,
you were always rushing, checking the time…
but now, look at you.
You’re different.
[QUINITO] You know, bro...
you and Kara look good together.
What's the status between the two of you?
Uh…
we just like...
spending a lot of time together
[QUINITO LAUGHS]
Is that "status"?
Well, we’re happy when we’re together
and we’re getting to know each other deeper.
Oh…
- the getting-to-know stage! - [JAO] Yes.
Something like that. [JAO CHUCKLES]
But you like Kara, don’t you?
I think Kara also likes you.
You think so?
Yeah!
I mean…
she’s happy when Jao is around.
And when Jao is away, she’s sad!
Really?
Really.
- He’s blushing! - [HAN BIN] Look at him!
[QUINITO AND HAN BIN LAUGH]
[QUINITO] Uh...
- Come on, raise your glass, man! - Let’s just drink to that.
- Cheers, cheers. - To you and Kara!
- Kara… Jao. - Cheers!
[SIARGAONON] Karajaw!
To me and Kara.
[HAN BIN EXHALES CONTENTEDLY]
[JAO COUGHS]
- Isn’t it delicious? - This is so strong.
- No. - [JAO CLEARS THROAT]
Thanks for coming with me on this tour, Ariel.
Anytime, Princess Pearl. Besides, Kara insisted.
[ARIEL] Miss Jen,
- [ARIEL] Miss Isabel, please drink some water! - [PEARL] Oh, here!
- [ARIEL] My sister will serve you. - [BYSTANDER] Oh my gosh, he's so hot!
[ARIEL] It’s so hot! It’s so hot in here!
- [PEARL] Here! - [ARIEL] But it’s so beautiful, look!
[ARIEL] Wow!
What a beautiful view.
Princess Pearl!
Han Bin oppa!
[ARIEL SPEAKS SIARGAONON] Take a look at that.
[ARIEL] Han Bin oppa!
[BYSTANDER] He’s hot!
Pearl!
I’ll help you!
[BYSTANDER] My bag is heavy, too!
[PEARL LAUGHS]
Wow! Your level of freshness is top notch today, Sir Han!
[PEARL] Is that a smile or a weapon?
Unique level achieved!
- [PEARL] Let’s go? - Let’s go!
[ARIEL] Okay, Miss Isabel, Miss Jen,
right here, please.
This is the beach of General Luna…
You’re early.
Hi, Kara.
I missed you.
[KARA] Hey! Archie!
[KARA] Long time!
When did you get back?
Just today. I left my bags at the hotel.
- And I came here... - Nice.
- to see you. - [KARA LAUGHS]
- I’ve missed you so much. - I’ve missed you!
[ARCHIE LAUGHS]
[KARA CHUCKLES]
[KARA] Uh...
Jao, this is Archie.
Archie, this is Jao.
I’m Jao.
Archie. Nice to meet you.
Archie’s my friend.
He goes back to the island whenever
there are volunteer programs or community works.
So, you’re here for vacation?
No, I’m here for Kara.
Ah.
Y-You guys are…?
Hanging out?
Right!
I forgot you have this "No Boyfriend" rule.
- No Boyfriend rule? - I thought you gave that up.
- No Boyfriend rule? - Hey, that’s not true!
- You just made that up! - [ARCHIE LAUGHS]
I never had a rule like that!
I missed you a lot.
- [KARA LAUGHS] - Haven’t been back in a while.
Yeah! You’re just all over the world.
Oh, I heard about your lectures this week.
At Farmers?
“Lecture” is a bit much.
It’s just a casual workshop.
[ARCHIE] It’s more of a cultural and sustainability immersion.
Nice.
Noah said you’re helping us out with the immersion.
Yeah. He told me about it.
Of course, I’ll help with logistics.
What do you do, man?
Hm? Me?
Nothing. Just hanging out.
Boring.
[JAO] My life is boring.
No, really. I’m interested.
Uh… I’m on vacation,
so I’m not really interested to talk about work.
[ARCHIE SCOFFS]
Um...
Archie, can I bring Jao along next week?
And his friend, too?
Yeah, man. Is that okay?
Sure. I’ll text you the schedule of the local immersion.
[ARIEL] This week’s storyteller is Quinito.
Let’s go, Storytellers of the Week!
My friend is amazing!
Right?
What made you decide to volunteer today, Quinito?
I was just curious. And... you know,
I didn’t want my Siargao experience to be just surfing and eating.
And I also want to give back to the kids
before I go back to Manila.
Manila?
You’re leaving?
I thought you’re staying here?
[ARIEL SPEAKS SIARGAONON] Exactly!
Um...
My friend and I are
opening our restaurant in Manila.
This is so sad, Quinito.
Bro, we’re really gonna miss you.
Promise, I’ll be back.
Well…
You need a send-off party.
[PEARL] There has to be one!
Game?
[PEARL LAUGHS]
Isn’t Archie amazing?
He only used to teach kids.
Now he’s running workshops for farmers.
Thanks for helping organize all this.
No problem.
[JAO] Excuse me.
Kara told me you work for Young Horizon?
You won’t stop until you find out what I do for a living, huh?
I'm just curious, bro.
Why?
Are you looking for a new job?
[ARCHIE SCOFFS] No.
No offense…
[ARCHIE] I wouldn’t work for Young Horizon.
Excuse me?
Bro, you’re coming off strong.
[ARCHIE SCOFFS]
I'm just curious if Kara knows what your company is really about.
Do we have a problem?
No.
No. We’re good.
Shall we start?
[ARCHIE] Please come in!
There’s something wrong with that guy.
I’ll take care of him.
Watch me.
We’ve prepared some compost materials,
so you guys can try it yourselves.
I’ll partner up with Jao.
[JAO] I just find it incredible
that the more I get to know you,
the more I discover how knowledgeable you are.
And I find your intelligence very attractive.
Do you know what that’s called?
[LEXI] Which, incidentally, is happening right here, right now?
They got chemistry, bro.
Do you like libraries?
Yes, Sir Han.
You’ve been to all the libraries you mentioned?
Someone messaged me, looking for a Song Ji Ho.
- [PEARL] Who’s that? - [ARIEL] I don't know!
[JAO] I like seeing you like this, Kara.
I like seeing you happy.
[KARA] I’m happy that you’re here, Jao.
I’m thankful you came back.